Guide to the Internation Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 814 records, 1958-1994 IBT0029
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Local 814 records
1943-1995
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
Kehoe, Vincent C.
IBT0029
1.5 Linear Feet
This collection contains materials produced by or amassed by Local teamsters union 814 dating from 1943-1995.
Arrangement
Organized into one series: Vincent Kehoe collection.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials produced by or amassed by Local teamsters union 814. The collection currently consists of material donated by former member Vincent Kehoe. Included are registrations and licenses, collective labor agreements, magazine issues, a Constitution and By-laws, a mileage guide, union directories and roster, pamphlets, and NY state laws and tariffs from 1943 to 1995.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Family of Vincent Kehoe, 2012 [2012.060]
Transportation; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions; Labor and laboring classes; Labor; Trucking; Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York -- History -- 20th century; Kehoe, Vincent C.
- Vincent Kehoe Collection, 1943-1995; Series 1
  Arrangement
  Arranged by subject
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains materials donated by Vincent Kehoe who was a member of IBT Local 814. It is comprised of a variety of personal, local-related, union-related, and miscellaneous materials. Included are Kehoe's daily driving logs, his vehicle registrations and licenses, collective labor agreements, magazine issues, a Constitution and By-laws, a mileage guide, union directories and roster, pamphlets, and NY state laws and tariffs. They range in date from 1943 to 1995. These materials provide interesting insight into the day to day activities of an IBT truck driver as well as information concering the local and union to which he belonged.
  - Daily Driving Logs, August, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Collective Labor Agreements, 1948-1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Collective Labor Agreements (Cont.), 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - International Teamster, September 1971-November 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Constitution and By-laws, July, 1949-September, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Wage Scales, March, 1952-March, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Joint Mileage, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Local 814 Application Blanks, 1950's (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - NY State Laws and Tariffs, July, 1954-1961 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Local 814 News, December, 1970-May, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Directories and Roster, 1956-April 1, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Pamphlets, 1952-May, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Vehicle Registrations and Licenses, 1943-1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)